Karen Shearer Collection, 1935-1996, bulk 1974-1992
Indiana University Digital Library Program
Karen Shearer Collection
1935-1996,
bulk 1974-1992
Indiana University, Archives of African American Music and Culture (AAAMC) Smith Research Center, Rooms 180-181 2805 E. 10th St. Bloomington, IN 47408-2601 Phone: 812-855-8547 Fax: 812-856-0333 Email: aaamc@indiana.edu http://www.indiana.edu/~aaamc
Shearer, Karen
SC 129
67 boxes
Collection consists primarily of interview transcripts, program transcripts, and artist publicity materials used in the production of the Westwood One Radio programs Special Edition, That's Country Music, Rock Chronicles, My Top Ten, and History of Rock 'n Roll. It also contains materials from various specials including programs on Elvis Presley, Jimi Hendrix, and the Rolling Stones.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research.
Biographical Note
Karen Shearer graduated from San Diego State University and began her career as a publicist for Capitol Records before moving to the Westwood One Radio Network circa 1980, where for the next decade she worked as a producer for Special Edition, a weekly program featuring the music of popular Black recording artists. During this period she also produced rock and country music programs for the Westwood One Radio Network. Shearer eventually left radio and the music business to produce wildlife programs for television.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in four series:
Series 1. Special Edition (radio program)
* Subseries 1.1. Interview Transcripts
* Subseries 1.2. Program Transcripts
* Subseries 1.3. Artist Publicity Materials
* Subseries 1.4. Artist Photographs
Series 2. Rock Chronicles (radio program)
* Subseries 2.1. Interview and Program Transcripts
* Subseries 2.2. Publicity Materials (print and photographs)
Series 3. That's Country Music (radio program)
Series 4. General Research Files
Scope and Content Note
This collection consists primarily of 67 boxes of documents and photographs pertaining to three of the Westwood One Radio Network's programs: Special Edition, a program that featured interviews with and music by a wide range of R&B artists, including the Temptations, Kool & the Gang, Luther Vandross, Aretha Franklin, Jermaine Jackson, Stephanie Mills, and Rick James; Rock Chronicles, a program that featured interviews and music of many popular rock music artists of the era; and That's Country Music which includes similar materials for country music artists.
The materials include interview transcripts from the aforementioned programs, as well as press releases and black and white publicity photographs of many of the artists interviewed on the programs. Also included are transcripts of the radio programs and other special programs produced by Westwood One Radio on Jimi Hendrix, The Rolling Stones and Elvis Presley.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in IUCAT, the IU Libraries' online catalog. Materials about related topics, persons or places can be found by searching the catalog using these terms.
Names
Presley, Elvis, 1935-1977
Rolling Stones
Westwood One
Subjects
African American musicians
African American musicians--Photographs
African American musicians--Interviews
Rhythm and blues musicians
Country musicians
Rock musicians
Funk musicians
Popular music--United States
Radio--Production and direction
Interviews (Sound recordings)
Radio programs
Related Material
The LPs of the airchecks composing Westwood One's Special Edition radio show are available through the Indiana University, Archives of Traditional Music (Accession numbers 92-206-B--92-255-B; shelf numbers 12 J 6303--12 J 6402). Cassette copies of the LPs are available through the AAAMC as part of its "Westwood One: Special Edition Collection" (SC 70).
Administrative Information
Acquisition Information
Donated by Karen Shearer to the AAAMC in June 2000.
Collection Inventory
- 1. Special Edition (radio program), 1975-1994
  - 1.1. Special Edition Interview Transcripts, 1975-1988
    - Abbott, Gregory, 1986 September 24, #4432A; 16 typed leaves (Box 1)
    - Abbott, Gregory, 1986 October 20, #4533; 23 typed leaves
    - Abbott, Gregory, 1987 January 15, #4713; 28 typed leaves
    - Abbott, Gregory, 1988 May 2, #6186; 18 typed leaves
    - Abrams, Colonel, 1986 April 2, #3914B; 30 typed leaves
    - Abrams, Colonel, 1987 July 23, #5334A; 16 typed leaves
    - Arrington, Steve (Slave), 1983 February 25, #1643A; 11 typed leaves
    - Arrington, Steve (Slave), 1985 May 5, #3013A; 16 typed leaves
    - Arrington, Steve (Slave), 1986 April 18, #3998B; 14 typed leaves
    - Arrington, Steve (Slave), 1987 October 26, #5673; 21 typed leaves
    - Ashford & Simpson, 1982 May 21, #1212; 14 typed leaves
    - Ashford & Simpson, 1983 July 25, #1876; 14 typed leaves
    - Ashford & Simpson, 1984 December 7, #2727B; 18 typed leaves
    - Atlantic Star, 1981 November 12, #954; 25 typed leaves
    - Atlantic Star, 1983 October 17, #2006A; 29 typed leaves
    - Atlantic Star, 1985 April 22, #2988; 27 typed leaves
    - Atlantic Star, 1986 February 10, #3727A; 28 typed leaves
    - Atlantic Star, 1987 March 24, #4937; 20 typed leaves
    - Austin, Patti, 1981 October 1, #885; 24 typed leaves
    - Austin, Patti, 1984 March 1, #2171; 27 typed leaves
    - Austin, Patti, 1985 October 28, #3515C; 20 typed leaves
    - Average White Band (Ferrone, Steve & Stuart, Hamish), undated, [unnumbered]; 4 typed leaves
    - Bailey, Philip (Earth, Wind & Fire), 1983 July 27, #1880A; 20 typed leaves
    - Bailey, Philip (Earth, Wind & Fire), 1984 October 30, #2579B; 19 typed leaves
    - Bailey, Philip (Earth, Wind & Fire), 1985 May 13, #3039B; 11 typed leaves
    - Bailey, Philip (Earth, Wind & Fire), 1986 March 6, #3811A; 21 typed leaves
    - Baker, Anita, 1984 January 4, #2095; 32 typed leaves
    - Baker, Anita, 1986 April 21, #3994A; 25 typed leaves
    - Baker, Anita, 1986 November 17, #4588; 8 typed leaves
    - Bar-Kays, 1982 February 19, #600; 26 typed leaves
    - Bar-Kays, 1984 July 17, #2418; 25 typed leaves
    - Bell, Regina, 1987 May 15, #5101; 14 typed leaves
    - Benson, George, 1981 October 11, #886; 28 typed leaves
    - Benson, George, 1983 June 29, #1834A; 17 typed leaves
    - Benson, George, 1984 December 13, #2743A; 21 typed leaves
    - Benson, George, 1988 August 15, #6533; 23 typed leaves
    - Berry, Chuck, 1987 October 1, #5570; 4 typed leaves (Box 2)
    - Bofill, Angela, 1980 May 27, #36; 25 typed leaves
    - Bofill, Angela, 1982 February 18, #1058; 19 typed leaves
    - Bofill, Angela, 1983 April 18, #1720A; 17 typed leaves
    - Bristol, Johnnie, 1982 April 29, #1170; 26 typed leaves
    - Brothers Johnson, 1981 June 30, #787; 22 typed leaves
    - Brothers Johnson, 1982 December 14, #1538; 34 typed leaves
    - Brothers Johnson, 1984 July 26, #2434; 27 typed leaves
    - Brown, Bobby (New Edition), 1987 April 13, #5014; 18 typed leaves
    - Brown, Bobby (New Edition), 1988 June 15, #6459; 13 typed leaves
    - Browne, Tom, 1981 July 7, #799; 18 typed leaves
    - Browne, Tom, 1983 October 31, #2025A; 17 typed leaves
    - Bryson, Peabo, 1982 July 29, #1304; 28 typed leaves
    - Bryson, Peabo, 1984 May 26, #2314; 26 typed leaves
    - Bryson, Peabo, 1986 October 31, #4589; 20 typed leaves
    - Bryson, Peabo, 1988 February 5, #5894; 13 typed leaves
    - Butler, Jerry, 1981 April 1, #650; 22 typed leaves
    - Cameo, 1983 June 15, #1818; 2 typed leaves
    - Cameo, 1985 November 1, #3508A; 17 typed leaves
    - Cameo, 1986 December 1, #4617B; 17 typed leaves
    - Carlton, Carl, 1982 October 5, #1422; 28 typed leaves
    - Carn, Jean, 1986 June 8, #4139B; 8 typed leaves
    - Champaign, 1981 March 20, #637; 13 typed leaves
    - Champaign, 1983 March 8, #1657; 22 typed leaves
    - Champaign, 1983 June 13, #1815C; 18 typed leaves
    - Champaign, 1984 October 17, #2584A; 24 typed leaves
    - Chi-lites, 1980 November 1, #540; 15 typed leaves
    - Chi-lites, 1983 April 6, #1708; 24 typed leaves
    - Chi-lites, 1984 March 15, #2189; 26 typed leaves
    - Clinton, George, 1983 January 7, #1574; 18 typed leaves
    - Clinton, George, 1984 February 1, #2124; 29 typed leaves
    - Club Nouveau, 1986 September 29, #4449B; 18 typed leaves
    - Club Nouveau, 1988 October 1, #6266; 16 typed leaves
    - Cole, Natalie, 1981 September 4, #842; 21 typed leaves
    - Cole, Natalie, 1985 May 2, #3008B; 24 typed leaves
    - Cole, Natalie, 1986 January 17, #3679; 18 typed leaves
    - Cole, Natalie, 1987 June 19, #4140; 26 typed leaves
    - Cole, Natalie, 1987 December 9, #5770; 14 typed leaves
    - Commodores, 1982 January 29, #1009; 29 typed leaves (Box 3)
    - Commodores, 1983 June 9, #1800; 19 typed leaves
    - Commodores, 1985 January 28, #2791; 18 typed leaves
    - Commodores, 1986 September 29, #4450; 30 typed leaves
    - Commodores, 1986 November 11, #4565; 17 typed leaves
    - Con Funk Shun, 1982 January 19, #1007A-B-C; 30 typed leaves
    - Con Funk Shun, 1982 October 22, #1455; 17 typed leaves
    - Con Funk Shun, 1983 December 11, #2079; 21 typed leaves
    - Con Funk Shun, 1985 June 7, #3093B; 22 typed leaves
    - Con Funk Shun, 1986 June 6, #4149B; 8 typed leaves
    - Cooper, Michael (Con Funk Shun), 1987 December 3, #5767; 16 typed leaves
    - Crawford, Randy, 1981 August 6, #813; 11 typed leaves
    - Crawford, Randy, 1982 May 18, #1203; 17 typed leaves
    - Crawford, Randy, 1983 October 5, #1985A; 15 typed leaves
    - Crusaders, 1981 November 9, #916; 28 typed leaves
    - Crusaders, 1983 April 28, #1752; 19 typed leaves
    - Crusaders, 1984 May 22, #2308; 23 typed leaves
    - Day, Morris (Time), 1982 October 18, #1433; 23 typed leaves
    - Day, Morris (Time), 1985 August 8, #3270; 12 typed leaves
    - Day, Morris (Time), 1988 January 13, #5812; 11 typed leaves
    - Dazz Band, 1982 July 6, #1258; 22 typed leaves
    - Dazz Band, 1984 January 31, #2130; 14 typed leaves
    - Dazz Band, 1984 September 27, #2561; 29 typed leaves
    - Dazz Band, 1986 July 2, #4261; 3 typed leaves
    - Dazz Band, 1988 May 27, #6276; 27 typed leaves
    - DeBarge, undated, #1768; 22 typed leaves
    - DeBarge, 1982 August 11, #1336; 15 typed leaves
    - DeBarge, 1985 April 9, #2972B; 23 typed leaves
    - DeBarge, 1986 May 8, #4052D; 25 typed leaves
    - DeBarge, Bunny, 1987 February 25, #4826B; 11 typed leaves
    - DeBarge, Chico, 1986 October 1, #4459; 12 typed leaves
    - DeBarge, Chico, 1987 October 6, #5585; 13 typed leaves
    - DeBarge, El, 1986 August 21, #4369B; 12 typed leaves
    - Deele, 1985 July 8, #3187; 16 typed leaves
    - Deele, 1987 July 10, #5305; 18 typed leaves
    - Deele, 1988 April 27, #6155; 20 typed leaves
    - Dells, undated, [unnumbered]; 8 typed leaves
    - Dells, undated, #551; 14 typed leaves
    - Dells, 1980 November 1, #551; 20 typed leaves
    - Dramatics, 1982 October 13, #1441; 27 typed leaves
    - Dramatics (Ron Banks), 1984 January 31, #2120; 24 typed leaves
    - E., Sheila (Escovedo), 1984 September 10, #2524A; 20 typed leaves (Box 4)
    - E., Sheila (Escovedo), 1985 September 6, #3332B; 20 typed leaves
    - Earth, Wind & Fire, 1981 January 20, #595; 21 typed leaves
    - Earth, Wind & Fire, 1987 November 4, #5678; 34 typed leaves
    - Edwards, Dennis (Temptations), 1984 February 29, #2162; 31 typed leaves
    - Edwards, Dennis (Temptations), 1984 May 3, #2272; 30 typed leaves
    - Emotions, 1984 July 11, #2412; 47 typed leaves
    - Fields, Richard "Dimples," 1987 August 12, #5407A; 13 typed leaves
    - Fields, Richard "Dimples," 1985 December 19, #3363B; 21 typed leaves
    - Fields, Richard "Dimples," 1982 November 17, #1496; 17 typed leaves
    - Fields, Richard "Dimples," 1982 July 14, #1277; 27 typed leaves
    - Five Star, 1986 January 30, #3708B; 20 typed leaves
    - Five Star, 1986 May 5, #4043; 6 typed leaves
    - Five Star, 1987 March 15, #4917; 18 typed leaves
    - Force MD's, 1984 November 26, #2700A; 10 typed leaves
    - Force MD's, 1985 May 28, #3083; 9 typed leaves
    - Force MD's, 1987 July 20, #5318; 11 typed leaves
    - Four Tops, 1981 September 21, #851; 27 typed leaves
    - Four Tops, 1982 August 26, #1364; 30 typed leaves
    - Four Tops, 1985 April 19, #2986A; 23 typed leaves
    - Franklin, Aretha, 1985 July 24, #3228C; 20 typed leaves
    - Franklin, Aretha, 1980 September 16, #416; 11 typed leaves
    - Full Force, 1986 March 10, #3906B; 23 typed leaves
    - Full Force, 1987 February 10, #4784; 2 typed leaves
    - Full Force/Lisa Lisa, 1985 July 3, #3179; 25 typed leaves
    - Full Force/Lisa Lisa, 1986 March 10, #3903; 13 typed leaves
    - Full Force/Lisa Lisa, 1987 April 15, #4998; 23 typed leaves
    - Gap Band, 1981 February 20, #606; 23 typed leaves
    - Gap Band, 1982 April 28, #1168; 14 typed leaves
    - Gap Band, 1983 January 18, #1583; 17 typed leaves
    - Gap Band, 1983 September 30, #1983; 21 typed leaves
    - General Caine (General Kane), 1986 September 15, #4416B; 18 typed leaves
    - General Caine (General Kane), 1987 July 9, #5319A; 24 typed leaves
    - Graham, Larry, 1981 August 4, #815; 21 typed leaves
    - Graham, Larry, 1983 June 30, #1835; 19 typed leaves
    - Green, Al, 1987 March 20, #4920; 31 typed leaves
    - Green, Al, 1988 November 2, #6786; 3 typed leaves
    - Guthrie, Gwen, 1986 July 21, #4272; 13 typed leaves
    - Hancock, Herbie, undated, #1141; 23 typed leaves
    - Hancock, Herbie, 1983 August 30, #1932A; 15 typed leaves
    - Hancock, Herbie, 1984 September 25, #2559; 21 typed leaves
    - Hayes, Isaac, 1986 December 10, #4623A; 11 typed leaves (Box 5)
    - Hendrix, Jimi, 1982 February 15, #5000; 8 typed leaves; Mitchell, Mitch
    - Hendrix, Jimi, 1982 February 15, #5001; 4 typed leaves; Mitchell, Mitch
    - Hendrix, Jimi, 1982 February 20, #5003; 7 typed leaves; Etchingham, Kathy
    - Hendrix, Jimi, 1982 February 20, #5004; 2 typed leaves; Etchingham, Kathy
    - Hendrix, Jimi, 1982 February 23, #5002; 25 typed leaves; Kramer, Eddie
    - Hendryx, Nona, 1975 August 28, #3319B; 22 typed leaves
    - Hendryx, Nona, 1983 April 6, #1703; 16 typed leaves
    - Hendryx, Nona, 1983 July 29, #1879; 24 typed leaves
    - Hendryx, Nona, 1984 June 18, #2355; 18 typed leaves
    - Hendryx, Nona, 1987 April 15, #5002; 10 typed leaves
    - Hewett, Howard (Shalamar), 1982 July 13, #1275; 25 typed leaves
    - Hewett, Howard, 1986 August 13, #4342; 24 typed leaves
    - Hewitt, Howard, 1987 February 26, #4837; 5 typed leaves
    - Hewitt, Howard, 1988 March 18, #6035; 20 typed leaves
    - Houston, Thelma, 1981 April 27, #699; 20 typed leaves
    - Houston, Thelma, 1983 March 15, #1671A; 23 typed leaves
    - Houston, Thelma, 1984 November 21, #2697B; 22 typed leaves
    - Howard, Miki, 1986 October 23, #4542B; 19 typed leaves
    - Howard, Miki, 1987 April 1, #4963A; 9 typed leaves
    - Howard, Miki, 1987 July 21, #5316; 24 typed leaves
    - Howard, Miki, 1987 November 17, #5735; 18 typed leaves
    - Hyman, Phyllis, 1981 June 19, #701; 15 typed leaves
    - Hyman, Phyllis, 1981 June 19, #701; 15 typed leaves
    - Hyman, Phyllis, 1983 March 4, #1655A; 23 typed leaves
    - Hyman, Phyllis, 1986 September 30, #4460B; 14 typed leaves
    - Hyman, Phyllis, 1987 January 30, #4755A; 19 typed leaves
    - Ingram, James, 1983 October 11, #1998B; 33 typed leaves
    - Ingram, James, 1984 May 1, #2268A; 17 typed leaves
    - Ingram, James, 1986 August 14, #4341; 10 typed leaves
    - Isley Brothers (Ernie & Marvin), 1983 October 17, #2005A; 17 typed leaves
    - Isley Brothers, 1985 September 10, #3430B; 14 typed leaves
    - Isley Brothers, 1987 January 16, #3662; 11 typed leaves
    - Isley Brothers (Jasper & Chris), 1988 January 14, #5821; 15 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Freddie, 1985 June 12, #3121B; 20 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Freddie, 1986 January 10, #3663C; 17 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Freddie, 1986 September 18, #4412A; 14 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Freddie, 1988 June 21, #6348; 22 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Janet, 1983 May 25, #1778B; 15 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Janet, 1984 July 19, #2416; 16 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Janet, 1986 January 28, #3709; 15 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Jermaine, 1982 July 16, #1284; 21 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Jermaine, 1986 February 27, #3798A; 18 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Latoya, 1983 August 9, #1901A; 21 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Latoya, 1984 May 23, #2319B; 18 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Marlon, 1987 August 17, #5437; 24 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Millie, 1981 September 30, #894; 22 typed leaves (Box 6)
    - Jackson, Millie, 1982 July 6, #1256; 22 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Millie, 1986 September 23, #4440; 22 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Rebbie, 1984 November 7, #2663B; 21 typed leaves
    - Jackson, Rebbie, 1988 January 1, #5863; 14 typed leaves
    - James, Rick, 1978 February 4, #158; 10 typed leaves
    - James, Rick, 1981 February 19, #609; 24 typed leaves
    - James, Rick, 1982 August 19, #1350; 21 typed leaves
    - James, Rick, 1985 June 14, #3129B; 28 typed leaves
    - James, Rick, 1988 June 20, #6343; 22 typed leaves
    - Jarreau, Al, undated, #5299; 8 typed leaves
    - Jarreau, Al, 1983 July 8, #1852; 20 typed leaves
    - Jarreau, Al, 1983 July 1, #1855; 11 typed leaves
    - Jarreau, Al, 1980 July 16, #408; 20 typed leaves
    - Jets, 1985 November 11, #3542; 20 typed leaves
    - Jets, 1986 February 26, #3795; 8 typed leaves
    - Jets, 1986 June 25, #4194; 22 typed leaves
    - Jets, 1986 October 29, #4530; 18 typed leaves
    - Johnson, Jesse, 1985 July 29, #3244; 21 typed leaves
    - Johnson, Jesse, 1986 October 6, #4473; 44 typed leaves
    - Johnson, Jesse, 1987 May 7, #5124; 12 typed leaves
    - Jones Girls, 1981 January 14, #556; 18 typed leaves
    - Jones Girls, 1978 February 4, #1002; 15 typed leaves
    - Jones Girls, 1983 September 28, #1973A; 19 typed leaves
    - Jones, Booker T., 1981 November 20, [unnumbered]; 15 typed leaves
    - Jones, Glenn, 1984 October 24, #2628B; 10 typed leaves
    - Jones, Glenn, 1984 December 13, #2769B; 9 typed leaves
    - Jones, Glenn, 1986 June 23, #4189; 32 typed leaves
    - Jones, Glenn, 1987 October 20, #5640; 12 typed leaves
    - Jones, Quincy, undated, [unnumbered]; 20 typed leaves
    - Jones, Quincy, 1986 February 3, #3718A; 33 typed leaves
    - Jones, Shirley (Jones Girls), 1986 June 16, #4182; 16 typed leaves
    - Kashif, 1983 February 10, #1659; 17 typed leaves
    - Kashif, 1983 June 15, #1861; 15 typed leaves
    - Kashif, 1984 March 2, #2170; 28 typed leaves
    - Kashif, 1985 November 7, #3522C; 15 typed leaves
    - Kashif, 1987 October 21, #5630; 21 typed leaves
    - Khan, Chaka, 1981 May 4, #682; 16 typed leaves
    - Khan, Chaka, 1984 November 5, #2656A; 24 typed leaves
    - Khan, Chaka, 1986 July 30, #4326B; 10 typed leaves
    - Khan, Chaka, 1986 August 7, #4318A; 12 typed leaves
    - King, B.B., 1979 December 29, [unnumbered]; 34 typed leaves (Box 7)
    - King, Ben E., undated, [unnumbered]; 15 typed leaves
    - King, Ben E., 1986 September 1, [unnumbered]; 5 typed leaves
    - King, Evelyn, 1979 July 1, #436; 10 typed leaves
    - King, Evelyn, 1983 March 14, #1669; 26 typed leaves
    - King, Evelyn, 1983 December 12, #2075; 29 typed leaves
    - King, Evelyn, 1984 April 18, #2244; 21 typed leaves
    - King Evelyn, 1984 October 13, #2611; 1 typed leaves
    - King, Eveyln, 1988 April 11, #6085; 26 typed leaves
    - Klugh, Earl, 1982 March 17, [unnumbered]; 21 typed leaves
    - Klymaxx, 1984 December 13, #2847A; 16 typed leaves
    - Klymaxx, 1985 November 20, #3586B; 21 typed leaves
    - Klymaxx, 1986 July 23, #4287A; 8 typed leaves
    - Klymaxx, 1987 July 14, #5311; 5 typed leaves
    - Knight, Gladys, 1981 April 16, #674; 20 typed leaves
    - Knight, Gladys, 1983 June 2, #1794; 44 typed leaves
      Pagination is 1-43 with 2 leaves marked as leaf 13).
    - Knight, Gladys, 1985 March 5, #2893; 29 typed leaves
    - Knight, Gladys, 1986 November 11, #4566B; 22 typed leaves
    - Knight, Gladys, 1986 November 19, #5732; 17 typed leaves + 1 index (1 leaf)
    - Kool & the Gang, 1981 September 21, #888; 27 typed leaves
    - Kool & the Gang, 1983 October 20, #2007A; 16 typed leaves
    - Kool & the Gang, 1983 November 28, #83-51; 7 typed leaves
    - Kool & the Gang, 1984 October 15, #2612; 27 typed leaves
    - Kool & the Gang, 1985 May 3, #85-22; 7 typed leaves
    - Kool & the Gang, 1986 October 15, #4499; 35 typed leaves
    - Kool & the Gang, 1986 December 3, #87-01; 5 typed leaves
    - L.T.D., 1981 November 11, [unnumbered]; 20 typed leaves
    - LaBelle, Patti, 1984 January 12, #2098; 23 typed leaves
    - LaBelle, Patti, 1985 March 21, #2919A; 9 typed leaves
    - LaBelle, Patti, 1986 May 19, #4075; 32 typed leaves
    - Lakeside, 1982 January 28, #1006; 29 typed leaves
    - Lakeside, 1987 April 13, #1710; 26 typed leaves
    - Lakeside, 1983 October 28, #2022A; 30 typed leaves
    - Lakeside, 1984 July 12, #2413; 28 typed leaves
    - Lakeside, 1987 April 14, #5004; 17 typed leaves
    - Lattisaw, Stacy, 1984 March 8, #2181; 23 typed leaves
    - Lattisaw, Stacy, 1986 September 30, #4462B; 9 typed leaves
    - Lattisaw, Stacy, 1988 February 26, #5974; 13 typed leaves
    - Laws, Ronnie, 1981 August 28, #845; 23 typed leaves (Box 8)
    - Laws, Ronnie, 1983 July 20, #1875; 14 typed leaves
    - Laws, Ronnie, 1985 January 15, #2776B; 18 typed leaves
    - Levert, Gerald, 1986 July 16, #4248B; 9 typed leaves
    - Levert, Gerald, 1987 February 10, #4786; 16 typed leaves
    - Levert, Gerald, 1987 June 29, #5282; 11 typed leaves
    - Little Richard, 1984 September 17, #2535; 33 typed leaves
    - Little Richard, 1984 October 11, #2593B; 13 typed leaves
    - Little, Cleavon, 1981 April 1, [unnumbered]; 22 typed leaves
    - Loose Ends, 1985 May 14, #3040A; 15 typed leaves
    - Loose Ends, 1986 September 30, #4466A; 17 typed leaves
    - Loose Ends, 1986 December 12, #4626B; 18 typed leaves
    - Loose Ends, 1988 May 25, #6265; 19 typed leaves
    - Lynn, Cheryl, 1981 August 12, #824; 25 typed leaves
    - Lynn, Cheryl, 1982 May 18, #1200; 14 typed leaves
    - Lynn, Cheryl, 1983 September 29, #1974A; 18 typed leaves
    - Lynn, Cheryl, 1985 July 7, #3192; 17 typed leaves
    - Lynn, Cheryl, 1987 August 24, #5449; 9 typed leaves
    - Madame X, 1987 September 22, #15525; 37 typed leaves
    - Madame X, 1987 October 1, [unnumbered]; 1 typed leaf
    - Madame X, 1987 November 16, #87-47; 8 typed leaves
    - Manhattans, 1986 June 25, #395; 15 typed leaves
    - Manhattans, 1981 August 4, #434; 22 typed leaves
    - Manhattans, 1981 June 9, #767; 6 typed leaves
    - Manhattans, 1983 January 28, #1609; 24 typed leaves
    - Manhattans, 1985 March 26, #2943A; 12 typed leaves
    - Manhattans, 1987 January 8, #4692; 17 typed leaves
    - Mathis, Jonny, 1983 June 1, #1790; 17 typed leaves
    - Maze, 1983 June 8, #1801B; 23 typed leaves
    - Maze, 1986 August 25, #4363; 18 typed leaves
    - Medlin, Joe, 1982 September 27, [unnumbered]; 25 typed leaves
    - Midnight Star, 1982 November 10, #1493; 18 typed leaves
    - Midnight Star, 1983 August 13, #1930B; 22 typed leaves
    - Midnight Star, 1984 December 12, #2735A; 22 typed leaves
    - Midnight Star, 1984 December 12, #2735A; 22 typed leaves
    - Midnight Star, 1985 March 19, #2921A; 17 typed leaves
    - Midnight Star, 1986 May 22, #4089; 22 typed leaves
    - Midnight Star, 1988 September 26, #6635; 26 typed leaves
    - Moore, Melba, 1981 November 9, #964; 27 typed leaves
    - Moore, Melba, 1982 November 1, #1492; 1 typed leaves
    - Moore, Melba, 1983 November 30, #2058; 24 typed leaves
    - Moore, Melba, 1985 March 5, #2868A; 21 typed leaves
    - Moore, Melba, 1986 June 27, #4207; 23 typed leaves
    - Moore, Melba, 1987 January 16, #4714A; 11 typed leaves
    - Moore, Melba, 1988 June 14, #6336; 15 typed leaves
    - Morgan, Meli'sa, 1986 August 17, #4345; 14 typed leaves (Box 9)